Subscribe, like and share.
Today's series exists in thanks to the support of its viewers.
If you want to be one of them, find your way in Patreon,
YouTube, PayPal and Stripe.
And we are grateful to our community.
In April, 38 years ago, an accident occurred in the nuclear power plant in Chernobyl.
It has been identified as the heaviest in the history of nuclear power.
But the problem is not only that.
The communist government of Bulgaria hides the information about the incident.
While the people on the streets are protesting,
people are eating with a bright light on the salad.
The radioactive cloud is over Bulgaria.
The communist nomenclature drinks mineral water and eats tested food.
Who will change the measures against radiation?
We will talk to Professor Dmitar Vatsov from NoBulgarian University.
He is the author of the research on the archaeology of Moral Debilism.
Hello, Professor Vatsov.
Hello.
Let's start chronologically.
This event is happening.